Finding Aid for the Horace Tapscott Papers PASC-M.0237
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound Recordings, Series 1.
  - Assorted Identified Sound Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney H.S., Part 2, Oscar Brown Quartet, 1972 April 23 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: The Beginning.
      Personnel includes: Oscar Brown; Azar Lawrence; CoJoe; Fritz Wise; Richard Herrera; Jack Folks. On container: Oscar Brown Quartet, Part 2.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 April 24 (Box 70)
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.); Will Connell, Black Musician., 1972 April 27 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Deon / Lorenjo Gartmon -- Emanon / Will Connell, Jr. -- One For Lee / Lorenjo Gartmon
      Personnel includes: Richard Herrera, bass violin; Damon Womack, percussion; Willie El Negro, trumpet; Lorenjo Gartmon, trombone; Will Connell, Jr., alto saxophone; Horace Tapscott, piano.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 May 4 (Box 70)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the Ark, May 7, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Compositions: Free Lester -- Eye of the storm.
      Personnel includes: Bobby Bradford, Will Connell, Jr.
    - Troubled Waters at Berkley (cont.) and The Quintet & Voice of UGMAA at Jordan High School, 1972 May 7 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Troubled Waters at Berkley / Max Roach and Abbey Lincoln -- The Giant Is Awakened / H. Tapscott -- Effie / Stanley Cowell.
      Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott, piano; David Bryant, bass; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Black Arthur, alto saxophone. On container: Part II.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, Part 1, 1972 May 7 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Calvary.
      Personnel includes: Jack Folks, tenor saxophone; Luther Keyes, poet; Linda Hill, voice. Part I.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, Part 2, 1972 May 7 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: The Creator Has A Master Plan -- Fatihia.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, Part 3, 1972 May 7 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Fatishia (cont'd) -- African Village.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, Part 4, OBJ - OBJ sextet, 1972 May 7 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: The Beginning -- This Earth -- Black Woman.
      Personnel includes: Oscar Brown, Jr.; Azar Lawrence; CoJoe; Fritz Wise; Jack Folks; Richard Herrea. Luther Keyes, poet; Nate Morgan, piano.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, Part 5, Will Connell, Jr. Sextet, 1972 May 7 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Deon -- Will Tune (theme) -- Moon In Leo -- Lift Every Voice -- Effie.
      Personnel includes: Lorenjo Garuman; Will Connell; Nate Morgan; Richard Herrea; Dayman Womack; Willie L. Samprit.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), Black Composers, Then & Now, 1972 May 9 (Box 70)
      Topic: Black Composers, Then & Now.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Mother's Day Concert: The ARK at Widney High School, May 14, 1972
      Compositions include: Impressions -- Oriental Flower -- Man From Tankinya -- Calvary -- Little A's Chant -- The Creator Has A Master Plan.
      Personnel includes: Glen Givens, Will, alto saxophone; Black Arthur, alto and soprano saxophone; Al Connely, tenor saxophone; Steve Meeks, baritone saxophone; Willie L., Mark Lott, trumpet; Lester Robertson, trombone; David Bryant, Richard, bass; Everett, Damond, drums; Horace Tapscott, piano and conductor. On container: Part I.
    - Mother's Day Concert: The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney High School, Part 1, 1972 May 14 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Impressions / John Coltrane -- Oriental Flower (half) / McCoy Tyner.
      On container: Part I.
    - Mother's Day Concert: The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney High School, Part I, 1972 May 14 (Box 70)
    - Mother's Day Concert: The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney High School, Part II, 1972 May 14 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Oriental Flower / McCoy Tyner -- Man From Tankinya (half) / McCoy Tyner.
      On container: Part II.
    - Mother's Day Concert: The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney High School, Part 2(cont.), 1972 May 14 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: The Creator Has A Master Plan / Pharoah Sanders -- Utoipoia.
      On container: Part 2 (cont.)
    - Ark at Widney, Mother's Day at Widney (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Motherless Chils and Calvery -- Little A's Chant -- The Creator Has A Master Plan (pt I).
    - Ark at Widney, Mother's Day at Widney, 1972 May 14 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: The Creator Has A Master Plan (pt II) -- Utopia / McCoy Tyner.
    - Ark at Widney, Mother's Day at Widney, 1972 May 14 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Man from Tankinya / McCoy Tyner
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 May 16 (Box 72)
      Horace Tapscott, instructor. Compositions include: Oriental Flower / McCoy Tyner [on tape: C.S. #51572 @ Widney] -- Seize the Time Black Man / E. Brown.
    - The ARK at the University of California - Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 May 20 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Oriental Flower / McCoy Tyner.
      On container: Part 3.
    - Full Moon Day Concert; The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney, Part II, 1972 May 28 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: The Dark Tree / Horace Tapscott -- Black Anthem -- Effie.
      On container: Part 2.
    - Full Moon Day Concert; The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney, Part II, 1972 May 28 (Box 70)
    - Full Moon Day Concert; The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney, Part I, 1972 May 28 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Search For Peace / McCoy Tyner -- Little Africa (Pt. 1) / Lino Hill.
      Personnel includes: Richard H., bass; Willie N., percussion and trumpet; Lino, piano; R. Roy, flute; Robert Beckett. On container: Part I.
    - Full Moon Day Concert; The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney, Part II, 1972 May 28 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Little Africa (Pt.2) / L. Hill -- Sunrise Sunset (Pt.1).
      Personnel includes: The ARK, plus, Lester Robertson, trombone; David Bryant, bass; Steve Meeks, baritone saxophone, percussion, sol.; Will Connel, alto saxophone; Linda H., voice. On container: Part II.
    - Full Moon Day Concert; The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney, Part III, 1972 May 28 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Sunrise-Sunset (Pt.2) -- Bird Song (Pt.1) / Lino.
      On container: Part III.
    - Full Moon Day Concert; The ARK [Arkestra] at Widney, Part IV, 1972 May 28 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Bird Song (Pt.2) / L. Hill -- The Dark Tree / Horace Tapscott -- Black Anthem / J.W. Johnson -- Effie.
      On container: Part IV.
    - Radio Program from tape: Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at St. Elmo's Village Festival #52574, on KPFK, Captain Midnite Show., 1972 May 30 (Box 70)
      Personnel includes the Oscar Brown Jr. Sextet: Ray Straughter, tenor saxophone; Ernest Straughter, piano and flute; Jesse Sharps, soprano saxophone; Roberto Miranda, bass violin; Oscar Brown, Jr., piano and vocals. Captain Midnite, disc jockey.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 May 30 (Box 70)
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 June 1 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Impressions / John Coltrane -- Jitterbug Waltz / Thomas "Fats" Waller -- In A Sentimental Mood, Mood Indigo, In A Mellow Tone, Don't Get Around Much Anymore, Sophisticated Lady / Duke Ellington (Maestro).
      Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott, piano and class instructor; David Bryant, bass; Everett Brown, Jr., drums.
    - The ARK at Midnoc at Rose's, Part I, 1972 June 4 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: And so.. -- Some Home -- Lester Plays Lester -- Sunrise-Sunset -- Motherless Child -- Cavalry.
      Personnel includes: Black Arthur, alto saxophone; Horace Tapscott, piano; Lester Robertson, piano; Lino, voice; Walter Savage, bass.
    - The ARK at Midnoc at Rose's, Part II, 1972 June 4 (Box 70)
      Compositions include: Not At All / C.C. -- Mode For John -- Oriental Flower / McCoy Tyner.
      Personnel include: Robert R., flute and piccolo; Will Connel, Jr., Alto saxophone and flute; Black Arthur, alto and soprano saxophone; Steven M., baritone saxophone; Willie N., Semaj, trumpet; David Bryant, Richard H., bass; Lester Robertson, trombone; Everett Brown, Jr., percussion; Lino, voice; Horace Tapscott, piano and conductor.
    - The ARK at Midnoc at Rose's, 1972 June 4 (Box 70)
      On container: Part Three.
    - Malcolm X Center Talent Show, 1972 August 25 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Aum, Venuc, Capricorn Rising -- Contemplation -- Dance Cadaverous -- Opposites -- The Promise -- Les Noirs Marchent -- Bachianas Brasileras -- Mean To Me -- I Want To Talk About You -- Monk In Wonderland -- Relate To What -- Battle At Armageddon -- Miss Ann -- You Don't Know What Love Is -- Pretty Eyes -- Poor Eric -- Exodus -- Dark Nebula -- Lush Life -- You Are Too Beautiful -- Autumn Serenade -- Autumn Leaves -- The Creator Has A Master Plan -- Another Earth -- The Lady.
      Side One: Hashii & Ittiwaa; Side Two: Chaga.
    - D.T.C.S, December 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      The giant is awakened.
    - Porter's Interview, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Radio show in 1979???
    - Elaine Brown, 1973 January 12 (Box 72)
      On container: Rhy. 1 (?)
    - Elaine Brown with Horns, 1973 January 16 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: And We Shall Meet Again -- Until We're Free -- To A Little Baby -- Can't Go Back -- I KNow Who You Are -- Jonathan.
    - Elaine Brown with Strings, 1973 January 17 (Box 70)
      Compositions: I Know Who You Are -- Jonathan -- Can't Go Back -- No Time -- All The Young And Fine Men -- We Shall Meet Again -- Until We're Free
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in Concert at Immanuel Church of Christ, 1973 April 29 (Box 70)
      Personnel includes: Adele Sebastian, flute; Jesse Sharps, Black Arthur, alto and soprano saxophones; Will Connell, alto saxophone; Bobby Bryant, Jr., tenor saxophone; Steven Meeks, baritone saxophone; Lester Robertson, Lorenjo Gortman, Dennis Robertson, trombone; Rufus Olivier, bassoon and alto saxophone; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Marcus Hill, wooden drum; David Bryant, bass; Linda Hill, piano; Bill Madison, percussion; Horace Tapscott, piano/conductor; Chaga, engineer. 7 1/2 ips.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in Concert at the Azz Izz, 1973 December 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Compositions: Hight Priest -- Mode for John -- Half and Half -- Lush Life -- Masters at Work / E.Straughter -- As a Child -- Departure / S.Cowell. soloists listed as well
      After hours. Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Adele Sebastian; Jesse Sharps; Rufus; Ernie; Steve; Lester Robertson; David; Mark; Moises; Linda Hill; Delbert; Everett Brown, Jr., drums.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in Concert at the Azz Izz, 1973 December 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Compositions: Mode for John -- Lush Life -- Crescent -- Hight Priest -- Half and Half / Charles Davis -- One for O.W. / Roberto MM.
      After hours (probably all of them). Personnel: Mark, Lester and Delbert not there - car failure; Rufus; Ernie; Horatio Tapscott; Jesse; Linda; David; Everett; Moises; Steve; Roberto Miranda; Adele Sebastian; Chaga - support. Tape 1 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in Concert at the Azz Izz, 1973 December 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Compositions: Mode for John -- Lush Life -- Crescent -- High Priest -- Half and Half / Charles Davis -- One for O.W. / Roberto MM.
      After hours (probably all of them). Personnel: Mark; Lester Robertson; and Delbert not there - car failure; Rufus; Ernie; Horatio Tapscott; Jesse; Linda; David; Everett; Moises; Steve; Roberto Miranda; Adele; Chaga - support. Tape 2 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the Azz Izz, 1973 December 15 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Compositions include: Dems Folks -- Something for Kenny / Elmo Hope -- Jungle Juice / Horace Silver -- Great House -- One for O.W.
      Personnel includes: Rufus; Jesse; Ernie; Lester; Steve; Mark; Roberto Miguel Miranda; David Bryant; Horace Tapscott; Linda-support.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the Azz Izz, 1973 December 16 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      After hours (Ark would come in after regular groups). Compositions: Jungle Juice -- Great House -- Peyote Song no.3 / Jesse Sharps.
    - Doing It - KNBC, 1974; pasc-m_0237_008_012; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:40:08) (Box 8, Case 12)
      Transcribed from container: "1974 / Horace Tapscott - piano & strings - Marshall intro / Children - L. Hill comp / Boogie Woogie Woman #1 / Boogie Woogie Woman #2 / " " " #3 / " " " #4 / " " " #5 / Lush Life - Billy Strayhorn / Mt. Zion / Thunder / Fishes & Fouls / Mt. Zion (take 1-3)" and "Black Arthur Blythe - Alto Sax / Everett Brown Jr. / David Bryant - Bass / Lester Robertson - Trombone / Horace Tapscott - Piano" and "KNBC Ch. 4 / Doin' It - "7 1/2 IPS Mono / Side 2" and "Doing It KNBC"
    - Leon Gardener, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - IUCC evening concert, 1974 February 24 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      The Day the Sky Cried -- House of Saud.
    - Trio: Tapscott, Hines, Palmer, 1974 April 12; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Al Hines; Arnold Palmer.
      Compositions: This is for Benny -- Lino's Pad -- Isle of Celia.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the El Sudan in Pasadena, 1974 April 16; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 3)
      Inside container: Channell (28) "Black Journal." Tony Brown, moderator. Dr. Frances Welsing, psychiatrist; Dr. William Shockey, physicist.
    - Horace is in Rone's room, 04/21/1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Recording Danainas's first lesson on the drums in the garage
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Malcolm X birthday, at Camp Kilpatrick in Malibu (Dadisi Sanyika's ?? Malc X Ctr??), 1974 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Compositions: Desert Fairy Princess -- It's Time / Max Roach -- On the Nile / Charles Tolliver.
      Personnel: Greg Tell, drums; Al Hines; Ernie Roberts; Jesse; Lester; Adele; Horace Tapscott; Michael Dett and Jihad, engineers.
    - Malcolm X birthday, 1974 May 19; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 4)
      PAPA at Camp Kilpatrick in Malibu (Dadisi Sanyika's?? Malc X CTR??)
      Personnel: Greg Tell, drums; Al Hines; Ernie Roberts; Jesse, Lester; Adele; Horace Tapscott, Michael Dettand and Jihad, engrs.
      Compositions: Desert Fairy Princess, It's Time (Max Roach), On the Nile (Charles Tolliver)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at St. Elmo's Village Festival, Also KPFK Captain Midnight Show with the Oscar Brown Jr. Sextet., 1974 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Compositions: Bakai -- It's Time.
      Personnel in concert includes: Adele; Jesse; Ernie; Steve Meeks; Wendell Williams, french horn; Lester R; David B; Al Hines; Salaam, perc and drums; Charles Weaver, congas; Linda Hill, vocalist; Chaga and Michael Dett, archives. Personnel on the radio includes: E and R Straughter; Jesse; Roberto MM; Oscar Brown Jr., piano; Efashala, vocalist.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at St. Elmo's Village Festival, Also KPFK Captain Midnight Show - Oscar Brown Jr. Sextet., 1974 May 25 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Personnel: Adele; Jesse; Ernie; Steve Meeks; Wendell Williams, French Horn; Lester R; David B; Al Hines; Salaam, perc and drums; Charles Weaver, congas; Linda Hill, voice; Chaga and Michael Dett, archives. extet personnel: E and R Straughter, Jesse, Roberto MM, Oscar Brown Jr., piano, Efashala, vocal.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, May 26, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Compositions: Mike's Tune (for Michael Dett) / Jesse Sharps -- Duke Ellington Medley.
      Personnel includes: Al Hines; Salaam Wa Nogundi, drums; Gary Bias, alto; Steve Meeks, bari and alto; Jesse, soprano; Louis Spears, cello; Lester Robertson; Wille Bolden, tb; Rosalyn Meeks, soprano; Voice (Steve's sister), David Bryant; Linda Hill, vocalist; Adele, flute and vocal.
    - California Aqui Venimos, 1974 June 6; pasc-m_0237_001_007; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:14:53) 10.5 inch (Box 1, Case 7)
      Personnel: Horace Tapsott, piano; Roberto Miranda, Bass; Dave Rodriguez, drums. Written and directed by Robbie T. Byrd. Production at Chapel of Peace Lutheran School (where Robbie and Renee taught).
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at he IUCC, 1974 June 30 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Compositions include: Peyote Song No.3 -- Mike's Tune -- Jitterbug Waltz -- Little Africa -- Black Anthem.
    - It came from the Cosmos, 1974 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Avalon-Carver Community Center. Personnel: Jesse Sharps; Gary Bias; Adele; Ernie Roberts; Derek Roberts; David B; Lester R.; Linda Hill; Horatio Tapscott and Chaga (A & R). Compositions: Be there (early "Mothership" - perhaps original name) -- J.O.B. / Herbie Baker -- Horacio / RMM -- Little A's Chant / Herbie Baker -- Little Boy, Why are you Crying? / Samuel Brown.
    - It came from the Cosmos: Avalon - Carver Community Center, 1974 July 6; open reel audio tape (Box 31, Folder 8)
      Personnel: Jesse Sharps, Gary Bias, Adele, Ernie Roberts, Derek Roberts, David B., Lester R., Linda Hill, Horace Tapsott, And Chaga (A&R)
      Compositions: Be There, (Eraly mothership - perhaps original name), JOB. (Herbie Baker), Horacio (RMM), Little A's Chant (Herbie Baker), Little Boy, Why are you Crying (Samuel Browne).
    - Possible bad tape, 07/08/1974 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Ark at the IUCC, 1974 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Compositions: On the Nile / Charles Tolliver -- Flight 17 -- Little A's Chant -- Be there (Mother Ship).
      Personnel: David B.; Alan Hines; Louis Spears, cello; Jesse Sharps, Soprano; Gary Bias, Ernie Roberts, Adele Sebastian, flute; Pamela Jackson, flute; Derek Roberts, drums; Richard Davis, tp; Horatio Tapscott, Charles Galloway (Chaga / Ali Jihad), engr. Notes: "Linda Hill, Lester Robertson incarcerated. Wendell Williams present. No instrument. All of this is due to a foul play by (white devils)."
    - ARK Record, 1974 August 1; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 5)
      Compositions: Mikes's Tune -- J.O.B. -- Pitters (???)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Ark at Muslim's Bazaar, 1974 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Compositions: On the Nile / C. Tolliver -- Be there (Mother Ship) / H. Tapscott -- Mike's Tune / Jesse Sharps -- Little Africa / Linda Hill.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Sunday Concert at the IUCC, 1974 October 27; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 6)
      Compositions: Horacio -- Masters at Work / E. Straughter.
      Tape 1 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Sunday Concert at the IUCC, 1974 October 27; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 7)
      Compositions: Spiritual Suite / arranged by H. Tapscott.
    - Juanita Cruz Music Rally, 1974 November 24 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      The Tiki Island on 37th and Western. PAPA. Personnel: Cokkie Harris; Aubrey Hart; Jesse; Gary B; Michael Session; Ernie Roberts; Steve Meeks; Lester R.; Ron Jackson; Robert James; Willie Bolden; Louis Spears; Davis B; Alan Hines, Fritz Wise, Werevu, Billy Childs, Linda Hill, Richard Davis, HT, cond. Compositions: On the Nile / Charles Tolliver -- Mike's Tune (for Michael Session) / Jesse Sharps.
      Notes: Michael Dett: "Willie Bolden was a long time friend of HT's who played trombone. A long time friend of the family. Cookie Harris was Billie Harris' lady." Written notes: ".a nightclub where no consideation is given to the artists. Acoustic Piano was damaged beyond belief." And. "Michael Session's first concert with the ARK."
    - I.U.C.C., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Charles Chandler, solist; Horace Tapscott, solist; Jesse Sharps, clarinet; Kamau T., world musician.
      Compositions: Blue Essence, Flight 17, Black National Anthem
    - Aubrey Hart's Concert, 1975 March 9; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 9)
      Church. Personnel: Aubrey Hart, Jr., flute; Michael Session, soprano sax; Charles, tenor sax; Billy Childs, piano.
      Tape contained in an envelope.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Chapman College, 1975 April 26; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 10)
      Compositions: On the Nile
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Chapman College, 1975 April 26; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Chapman College, 1975 April 26; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 12)
      Lift Every Voice / James Johnson -- Eternal Egypt / Ernie Roberts.
      Tape 3 of 3.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1975 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Compositions include: Eternal Egypt / Ernie Roberts -- Lately's Solo -- National Anthem.
      Personnel includes: Adele; Aubrey; Jesse; Michael; Charles; Ernie; Amos; Lester; David B.; Werevu, ?Cole, Chaga and Tony Hills, engrs. 2 copies.
    - PAPA recording session for Theme Records, 1976 January 24; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Audiotronics Recording Studios in Covina, CA.
      Compositions: Eternal Egypt.
      Tape 4 of4.
    - PAPA recording session for Theme Records, 1976 January 24; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 13)
      Audiotronics Recording Studios in Covina, CA. Personnel: Charles Chandler; Wendell Williams; Horatio Tapscott??
      Compositions: Ancestral Echoes
      Also, Compositions: Joannette / Guido Sinclair -- Eternal Egypt -- Why Dont you Listen / HT -- Sketches of Drunken Mary -- Goat and Ram Jam / Jesse S.
    - PAPA recording session for Theme Records, 1976 January 24; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 14)
      Compositions: Why Don't You Listen.
    - PAPA recording session for Theme Records, 1976 January 24; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 15)
      Compositions: Joanette.
    - Pan American People Arkestra, 1976 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Compositions include: Back Beat / Horace Silver -- Ole / John Coltrane -- House of Saud / Charles Tolliver -- Half & Half / C. Davis -- Ancestral Echoes / Horace Tapscott -- Milestones / Miles Davis.
    - Concert at the Great House, 1976 March 20; 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Personnel: Herbert Callies, acl; Jesse Sharps, ss; Ernest, ts, Michael Sessions, as, Adele, flute and vocals, Aubrey Hart, fl, Amos Delone, bari, Al Hines, b, David B., Ishmael Balaka, perc, congas, Bill Madison, drums, perc, Werevu Isheguru, perc, Wendell Williams, fr horn, Horace Tapscott piano
      Compositions: Along the Nile -- Half and Half -- Eternal Egypt -- Little Boy Why are you crying? / Samuel Brown -- Black Woman I love you / Kamau and Nate Morgan -- Quagmire 5 am -- the Goat and the Ram Jam -- Buckwheat and syrup (that's Michael and Adele) -- Ole.
    - Concert at the Great House, 1976 March 20; 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)